

VINCENT OKEKE

Project Management | Marketing | Business

PROFILE

I am a highly tech savvy professional who has worked in a number of local and international organizations. My core skills include business and marketing strategy/consultancy, and project management. I possess a total of 10 years post-graduate professional work experience.

CONTACT

Phone: +234 806663 1119

Email: okekevincent@gmail.com

Add.: 5 Afusat Kekere Ekun,
 Addo, Ajah, Lagos

Web.: www.vincentokeke.com

BIODATA

Country of Origin: Nigeria

Date of Birth: 30/12/1988

Gender: Male

Marital Status: Married

EDUCATION

Master in Human Resource and Industrial Relations (MHRIR)

Lagos State University, Ojo | 2014 - 2016

Bachelor of Art, Mass Communications

Anambra State University, Uli | 2005 – 2009

PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATIONS

- Institute of Strategic Management (ISMN): Associate Member (2013)
- Nigerian Institute of Management, (NIM): Graduate Member (2011)
- Advertising Practitioners Council of Nigeria: Associate Member (2014)

EXPERIENCE

Dovichi Worldwide Technology Company Limited

Lead Strategist | 2015 - Date

To oversee the overall business operations and ensure steady positive growth. Lead and motivate team members to advance employee engagement and develop a high performing managerial team.

Unicaf

Digital Marketing Consultant | 2015 - 2018

Providing services on growth-hacking and special project execution. Some of the areas i work on include Marketing (Strategy, planning and executive), Strategic partnership implementation.

e-Scape Technologies Limited

Marketing & Business Strategist (VAS) | 2013 - 2015

Digital marketing, and business development with OEM and ODM partners. Enhancing strategic partnerships for product growth, market research.

REFERENCES

Oleka Bright gentlebright007@gmail.com 234 8068319302 Product Director | Judy Legal Michael Ohadugha mikelozytex@yahoo.com 234 8062895692 Founder | Soft.ng